 [
    {
      "id": 1,
       "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "He was very tired, so he went to ___ early.",
      "options": ["bed", "home", "rest", "sleep"],
      "answer": "bed"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "They always ___ the bus to school.",
      "options": ["take", "ride", "drive", "walk"],
      "answer": "take"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "I need to ___ for my keys. I can’t find them.",
      "options": ["look", "search", "look for", "find"],
      "answer": "look for"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "My brother is very ___ — he tells great jokes!",
      "options": ["funny", "fun", "happy", "friendly"],
      "answer": "funny"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "We usually have lunch in the school ___.",
      "options": ["canteen", "kitchen", "room", "hall"],
      "answer": "canteen"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "The opposite of 'cheap' is ___.",
      "options": ["expensive", "rich", "nice", "bad"],
      "answer": "expensive"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "She is afraid of ___.",
      "options": ["heights", "high", "top", "mountain"],
      "answer": "heights"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "We ___ up at 7 a.m. every day.",
      "options": ["get", "wake", "stand", "get up"],
      "answer": "get up"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "He works in a hospital. He’s a ___.",
      "options": ["nurse", "scientist", "teacher", "driver"],
      "answer": "nurse"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
        "level": "A2",
        "skill": "vocabulary",

      "question": "Don’t be ___ — wait for your turn!",
      "options": ["impatient", "quiet", "kind", "calm"],
      "answer": "impatient"
    }
  ]
